Hello! This is Shitao Miu~
안녕하세요 시타오미우입니다~~
Tada!
짠!
I made a map of the places that I have visited in Yamaguchi!
이번엔 제가 지금까지 다녀온 야마구치의 스팟을 모은 야마구치 미우맵을 만들어봤어요!
Yay! How is it?
예이! 어때요?
Yume hana haku on 24th will be in the Kirara Dome, right here,
이번에 24일에 있을 유메하나하쿠는 키라라 돔, 여기에서 있어요
And the Yamaguchi Tour Concert will be...
그리고 야마구치 투어는
around here. Shuunan Bunka Kaikan. Around here.
이 근처에요. 이 근처에서 개최됩니다. 슈난문화회관 이 근처에 있어요
So I don't think you can visit all the places in one day.
네. 그러니까 하루만에 이렇게 흩어져있는 야마구치현 전부를 가시기는 어려울거에요
So...
그러니까
When you come to Kirara Dome on the 24th,
키라라돔에 24일에 오실 때에는
visit half of them,
반틈을 가고
and when you come to Shuunan Bunka Kaikan,
슈난 문화회관
you can visit this half.
야마구치투어에 오실 때에는 이 쪽을 가신다거나
If you are visiting 2 to 3 days or longer,
삼일이나... 이틀정도?
I hope you can visit all the places.
장기로 오시는 분들은 전부 가 보셨으면 좋겠어요 ㅎㅎ
Especially the Himawari(Sunflower) Road and Tsunoshima are good places to visit in summer,
히마와리로드(해바라기길)이나 츠노시마는 특히 여름에 와 주셨으면 하는 스팟이니까
so if you have the chance to visit Yamaguchi in summer, please visit thouse places
여름에 야마구치에 오실 기회가 있으신 분은 꼭 가 보세요
You can probably enjoy Tsunoshima any time of the year.
츠노시마는 아마 언제 가셔도 즐기실 수 있을 거에요
Let me tell you about the places that I especially recommend.
제가 특히 추천하는 장소를 말씀드릴게요
My favourite place is...
제가 갈 때마다 들뜨는... 되게 좋아하는 장소는 여기
this place: Irori Sanzoku.
이로리 산조쿠 입니다
It's in the mountains
여기는 산이...
It's a restaurant..
식사하는 곳인데요....
It's like a restaurant in the mountains. It's a wonderful place,
말하자면 산에 있는 레스토랑같은.. 되게 멋진 곳이니까
so please visit.
꼭 가 보세요
Perhaps not on rainy days.
비 오는 날에는 안 가시는게 좋을지도 모르겠네요
And there are also soul foods, like kawarasoba, or barisoba. So I hope you get a chance to taste them.
그리고 역시, 기와소바 라든가 바리소바같은 소울푸드도 부디 드시고 돌아가셨으면 좋겠네요
And my favourite: Toushirou
제가 제일 좋아하는 토우시로우!
It's a place that sells uirou (a kind of Japanese dessert)
우이로우(일본 과자 종류) 가게인데요
You can find it in the airport, so please, please, bring it home as a souvenier!
이건 공항에도 있으니까 기념품으로 꼭! 꼭! 사서 가세요
I recommend the nama uirou so... try that one
생 우이로우가 추천이니까 생 우이로우를... 부디...
Is that all...?
이상인가요...?
So please visit Yamaguchi with this map! I'll wait for you~~
이걸 가지고 야마구치현에 꼭! 와주세요 기다릴게요~~